Fate. Dreams. These unstoppable ideals are held deep
in the heart of man. As long as there are people who seek
freedom in this life, these things shall not vanish
from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds. I don't care
what they say because I'm dreaming of you. You are the
treasure.
What's wrong, huh? You've had that brooding look on
your face for a while. Yeah, I guess I hoped I was
dreaming. About what? This may sound crazy, but it
seems to me we're not even moving. You feel that?
Now that you mention it, the sail doesn't appear to be
catching any wind at all.
No! We're screwed! We've entered the Calm Belt! The
Clam Belt? What's that? Calm Belt! A part of the sea
where nothing moves a muscle! So there's muscles and
clams? No!
What
was that, an earthquake? A good trick since we're at
sea. All of this chit-chat isn't going to get us out of
here. Fold the sails and start paddling now. We have to
get back on course. You can count on me! Don't panic.
And besides, this is a sailboat. Why do we need to
paddle? True. Look, there's no time to argue. Just
shut up and do as I say. At least it's nice and quiet
here. Fine, if I need to explain it to you, I will. In our
haste to escape from the Marines, we ended up going too
far south, and now we're off course and stuck out here.
So we enter the Grand Line? Woo-hoo-hoo! If we were at
the Grand Line, you think I'd waste my time explaining
this? Now look. The Grand Line is sandwiched in the
middle between these two green areas you see here, you
understand? These areas, just as they're labeled,
are what's called the Calm Belt. That's where we are.
Nobody knows why, but inside the Calm Belt, there's no
wind and no current. It's like a void where
everything's stagnant. Given that sailboats move by
catching winds, this is more than a dangerous region,
it can be fatal, get it? Nope, but it sounds like we're
in big trouble. Well, that explains why we haven't
gotten a single gust of wind. How are we going to get out
of this if our ship can't move? Maybe the wind will
start blowing again. Wind never blows in the Calm
Belt. And that's not all. There's another good reason
that people call this area dangerous. It's infested
with... What was that?
Here they come!
Sea monsters! They're gigantic!
The Calm Belt is also home to the Sea Kings! It's their
main place for breeding! They're the biggest reason
people can't cross the Calm Belt! any idea how we get
out of this? Yes. Everybody, don't move a muscle. We
don't want to give them any reason to stick around or
eat us. Once they're gone, we'll paddle back. Got it?
You call that a plan?
Shut up! Sorry.
That didn't improve anything! It sounds like it's
gonna! Waste yourselves, I think this behemoth's
gonna sneeze! No!
In case you haven't noticed, we are flying! Oh
well, at least we're back on our original course.
According to the map, we should be spotting the red
line any time now.
Wow, we're almost there, the grand line at last! Isn't
this exciting? We're finally going! We did it! We did
it! Cut it out! Sorry. Zoro! You must be right. Is the
path to the Grand Line really as perilous as it's drawn
here? Stop that!
Take a look. I'm familiar with the rumors, and these
drawings confirm it. As unimaginable as it may seem,
the entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain.
Mountain? So what, did we crash into it? You gotta be
kidding. I didn't believe it, but the map's clear. The
mountain appears to be riddled with small canals, so
we might have to go up and over it. Sounds like fun. What
are you talking about? Even if there are canals or
whatever, a ship can't climb up a mountain. Well, the
map says otherwise. That's right, and if Nami thinks
something can be done, then it can't, got that? Yeah,
but remember, that map was stolen from Buggy the
Clown, so can we trust if... In case they've noticed
the rudder's stuck, a little help over here be nice!
Sanji, would you please give Usopp a hand? I can't
think with all his shouting. It's terrible right
away, Nami! Okay. Uh, does this current seem
unusually strong to anyone else? Usopp, what did you
just say? I asked if any of you noticed the insane
strength of this current. The current? That must
be... What is it? The canals do go up the mountain. Oh,
come on. How could that possibly work? Look right
here. You see? The guiding light was directing us
toward this spot on the red line. Notice how it's
labeled here. Reverse mountain. Hello? Little help
over here, thank you! These green lines represent
canals or artificial waterways. If major currents
from all four oceans flow toward this mountain, what
do you think's gonna happen? The currents would force
water up these canals, collide at the top, and then
flow straight down into the Grand Line. Now, Reverse
Mountain is a winter mountain, so it's cold, right?
That means any surface currents that don't flow up the
canal will be forced down as they cool. Anything
riding those currents would be pulled down as well. If
we screw up and miss the entrance to the canal, the
Going Mary will be carried straight into the Red
Line's rock face and likely be destroyed. Ship and
crew would be sucked to the bottom of the sea.
Understand? Yeah. Basically, it's a mystery
mountain.
No, that's not my point at all. Anyway, since we're
positioned on this current, we shouldn't run into any
problems getting to the summit of Reverse Mountain.
Only thing that would hurt us now is if something went
wrong with the rudder. Nami, you're a genius! Call me a
skeptic, but ships do not climb mountains. Well, I've
heard a few stories. Stories about the Mystery
Mountain? No. What I have heard is that more than half
the people who try to make it to the Grand Line die
before they even get there. Whatever we find, it isn't
going to be easy. Sanji, could you get the sail?
Anything for you, Nami! Luffy, help me!
Got it!
Hey! I can see the mystery mountain!
That's insanely huge! Wow! Awesome! It's bigger than
I thought! I can't see the top! It's taller than the
clouds!
We're
getting sucked in! Hold the rudder steady! We're on
it! Nami! Where's that entrance you were talking
about? If we keep this heading, we're gonna crash into
the rocks!
There's a crack in that cliff. That must be it. Nami!
Give us a direction! Keep bearing straight ahead! You
can't be serious! Trust me! Have we made it? Is that the
canal entrance? More than likely. I've got to be
dreaming. It's impossible. The ocean really is
flowing up the mountain.
We have to make our way through those water gates just
right! Or we'll crash into the red line if he's smashed
to pieces!
We're drifting off course! Gotta go more to the right!
Right! Go right? Who hit starboard? Come
on now! Put your back into it! Gah!
Dumb
gum balloon!
Luffy! Drop a hold!
Now
it's just a screenshot to the
stomach! Wow, great view!
Whoa!
Look how high we are! We're in the
clouds!
This is insane!
We're not in the clouds, we're above them!
It's amazing!
We've done it! We've reached the summit!
I can see it! This is the greatest sea in the whole
world! The Grand Line! Somewhere out there the One
Piece is waiting and we're gonna find it! Let's
go!
Did you guys just hear something? It was probably just
the wind! At this speed, everything sounds
distorted!
What was that? Nami! I see a mountain up ahead! What?
That's impossible! But it's right there! I can see it!
Who cares? Go! After we pass the twin capes up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
It's a black wall! No, it's not! Then what is it?
It's a whale! What are we gonna do? Should we fight?
Idiots, how are we supposed to fight a hundred ton
whale? We have to do something! Our path is blocked!
How do we escape? Calm down. If this creature looks
like a giant wall to us, we must be a speck! That's
right! It's highly possible that this thing isn't
even aware that we're here! We'll run right into it
unless we change course! Look! We can get by on the
left! Port! Port to port! The rudder's broken! Do
something! Anything! Wait! I know! This'll work! It
has to! Hey! Luffy, what are you doing?
This is pointless! The ship's not gonna turn! Damn it!
Don't give up!
Is this the end? The cannon!
Done.
Or
is it? Or is it? Hey, that was my special scene!
Damn! Let's get out of here before it's too late!
Someone mind telling me what the heck is going on! It's
so big that the cannonball didn't even make it flinch.
That or his reaction time's really slow. Who cares? At
least we're alive!
My ears! Just battle! We have to get away from here!
Luffy? You think you can break my special seat and get
away with it? Take this! You moron!
I'm not through with you! There's a lot more with it!
I am not gonna die!
Oh, man. Everyone's been swallowed whole. Hey, you!
Can you hear me? Spit them out! I want my friends! Damn
you! Where do you think you're going, you jerk? You
give them back right now, you will! Listen, you big
boot, I'm not gonna ask again! Stop sinking, I mean it!
My friends and me are on an important adventure! I
can't lose them! Give them back!
So,
what do you think? I don't know what to think. Is this
even real? Because I know exactly what I saw and what I
felt. We were swallowed by the whale.
Is this a dream? Yeah, I'd say that's a fair guess.
Then what's with this island and the house?
Illusions.
Um, that looks like... A great game square!
Looks like someone's home. Let's hope it's a person.
I've had it. Let's go. Giant squids, guys with
harpoons? And where is Luffy? Yeah, where
is he? I don't know much about whales, but since when do
they have doors and lighted hallways?
A ship. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! We
should fire our cannon there! Now! No. Hold on a sec.
Someone's coming out.