Fate. Dreams. These unstoppable ideals are held deep
in the heart of man. As long as there are people who seek
freedom in this life, these things shall not vanish
from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds I don't care what
they say because I'm dreaming of you You are the
treasure I found So bright, so bold, it's so elusive
It's hard to look away Even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe how I feel inside I'm
really, really stuck on you I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem. And I won't stop till I get
there, you will see. You're all I need to have the
strength to believe. Believe in one.
I'm going to follow my dreams, however crazy they
seem. I'm going to share them with you, a love so true.
You're all I want, together we can move on, live how we
want to. There is no limit to us, we have the power of
love. We don't want to live ordinary lives. We have the
chance to live in paradise.
What's wrong, huh? You've had that brooding look on
your face for a while. Yeah, I guess I hoped I was
dreaming. About what? This may sound crazy, but it
seems to me we're not even moving. You feel that?
Now that you mention it, the sail doesn't appear to be
catching any wind at all.
No! We're screwed! We better the calm belt! The clam
belt? What's that? Calm belt! A part of the sea where
nothing moves the muscles! So there's muscles and
clams? No!
What was that? An earthquake? A good trick since we're
at sea. All of this chitchat isn't going to get us out of
here. Fold the sails and start paddling now. We have to
get back on course. You can count on me. Don't panic.
And besides, this is a sailboat. Why do we need to
paddle? True. Look, there's no time to argue. Just
shut up and do as I say. At least it's nice and quiet
here. Oh, fine. If I need to explain it to you, I will. In
our haste to escape from the Marines, we ended up going
too far south, and now we're off course and stuck out
here. So we enter the Grand Line? Woo-hoo-hoo! If we
were at the Grand Line, you think I'd waste my time
explaining this? Now look. The Grand Line is
sandwiched in the middle between these two green
areas you see here. You understand? These areas, just
as they're labeled, are what's called the Calm Belt.
That's where we are. Nobody knows why, but inside the
Calm Belt, there's no wind and no current. It's like a
void where everything's stagnant. Given that
sailboats move by catching winds, this is more than a
dangerous region. It can be fatal, get it? Nope, but it
sounds like we're in big trouble. Well, that explains
why we haven't gotten a single gust of wind. How are we
gonna get out of this if our ship can't move? Maybe the
wind will start blowing again. Wind never blows in the
Calm Belt. And that's not all. There's another good
reason that people call this area dangerous. It's
infested with... What was that?
Here they go!
You monsters! They're gigantic!
The Calm Belt is also home to the Sea Kings! It's their
main place for breeding! They're the biggest reason
people can't cross the Calm Belt! Any idea how we get
out of this? Yes. Everybody, don't move a muscle. We
don't want to give them any reason to stick around or
eat us. Once they're gone, we'll paddle back. Got it?
You call that a plan?
Shut up! Sorry.
That didn't improve anything! It sounds like it's
gonna! Face yourself, I think this behemoth's gonna
sneeze! No way!
It feels like we're flying! In case you haven't
noticed, we are flying! Oh
well, at least we're back on our original course.
According to the map, we should be spotting the red
line any time now.
Well, we're almost there! The red line at last! Isn't
this exciting? We're finally going! We did it! We did
it! Cut it out! Sorry. Zoro! You must be right. Is the
path to the Grand Line really as perilous as it's drawn
here? How's that?
Take a look. I'm familiar with the rumors and these
drawings confirm it. As unimaginable as it may seem,
the entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain.
Mountain? So what, did we crash into it? You gotta be
kidding. I didn't believe it, but the map's clear. The
mountain appears to be riddled with small canals, so
we might have to go up and over it. Sounds like fun. What
are you talking about? Even if there are canals or
whatever, a ship can't climb up a mountain. Well, the
map says otherwise. That's right, and if Nami thinks
something can be done, then it can. Got that? Yeah, but
remember, that map was stolen from Buggy the Clown, so
can we trust it? It's known as the Rudderstock. A
little help over here be nice. Sanji, would you please
give Usopp a hand? I can't think with all his shouting.
Hey, Nami! Okay. Uh, does this current seem unusually
strong to anyone else? Usopp, what did you just say? I
asked if any of you noticed the insane strength of this
current. The current? That must be... What is it? The
canals do go up the mountain. Oh, come on. How could
that possibly work? Look right here. You see? The
guiding light was directing us toward this spot on the
red line. Notice how it's labeled here, reverse
mountain. Hello? Little help over here, thank you.
These green lines represent canals or artificial
waterways. If major currents from all four oceans
flow toward this mountain, what do you think's going
to happen? The currents would force water up these
canals, collide at the top, and then flow straight
down into the Grand Line. Now, reverse mountain is a
winter mountain, so it's cold, right? That means any
surface currents that don't flow up the canal will be
forced down as they cool. Anything riding those
currents would be pulled down as well. If we screw up
and miss the entrance to the canal, the Going Mary will
be carried straight into the Red Line's rock face and
likely be destroyed. Ship and crew would be sucked to
the bottom of the sea, understand? Yeah, basically
it's a mystery mountain. No, that's not my point at
all. Anyway, since we're positioned on this current,
we shouldn't run into any problems getting to the
summit of Reverse Mountain. Only thing that would
hurt us now is if something went wrong with the rudder.
Nami, you're a genius! Call me a skeptic, but ships do
not climb mountains. Well, I've heard a few stories.
Stories about the Mystery Mountain? No. What I have
heard is that more than half the people who try to make
it to the Grand Line die before they even get there.
Whatever we find, it isn't going to be easy. Sanji,
could you get the sale? Anything for you, Nami! Luffy,
help me!
Got it!
Hey! I can see the Mystery Mountain! That's insanely
huge! Wow! Awesome! It's bigger than I thought! I
can't see the top! It's taller than the clouds!
We're all for getting sucked in! Hold the rudder
steady!
We're on it! Nami!
Where's that entrance you were talking about? If we
keep this heading, we're gonna crash into the rocks!
There's a crack in that cliff. That must be it. Nami!
Give us a direction! Keep bearing straight ahead! You
can't be serious! Trust me! Have we made it? Is that the
canal entrance? More than likely. I've gotta be
dreaming. It's impossible. The ocean really is
flowing up the mountain.
We have to make our way through those water gates just
right! Or we'll crash into the red line if he's smashed
to pieces!
Come
on now, put your back into it! The ladder!
I'm gone!
Grab a hold!
We made
it!
Now it's just a straight
shot to the stomach! Wow! Great view!
Wow! Look how high we are! We're in the clouds!
We're not in the clouds! We're above
them! It's amazing! We've done it! We've reached the
summit!
I
can see it! This is the greatest sea in the whole world!
The Grand Lie! Somewhere out there the One Piece is
waiting and we're gonna find it! Let's
go! Did
you guys just hear something? It was probably just a
whiz! At this speed, everything sounds distorted!
Nami! I see a mountain up ahead! What? That's
impossible! But it's right there! I can see it! Who
cares? Go! After we pass the twin caves up ahead, there
should be nothing but ocean!
It's a black wall! No, it's not! Then what is it?
Should we fight? Idiots? How are we supposed to fight a
hundred ton whale? Do something! Our path is blocked!
How do we escape? Calm down! If this creature looks
like a giant wall to us, we must be a speck! That's
right! It's highly possible that this thing isn't
even aware that we're here! We'll run right into it
unless we change course! Look! We can get by on the
left! Port! Port to port! The rudder's broken! Do
something! Anything! Wait! I know! This'll work! It
has to! Hey! Luffy, what are you doing?
This is pointless! The ship's not gonna turn! Dammit!
Don't give up!
Or is grown. This is
it. Hey, that was my special
scene!
Damn! Let's get out of here before it's too late! Who am
I telling me what the heck is going on? It's so big that
the cannonball didn't even make it flinch. That or his
reaction time's really slow. Who cares? At least
we're alive!
My ears! Just battle! Get away from here!
You think you can break my special seat and get away
with it?
I'm not through with you! There's a lot more with it!
Shut
up before you kill us!
I
am not
gonna die!
Oh, man. Everyone's been swallowed whole. Hey, you!
Can you hear me? Spit them out! I want my friends! Damn
you! Where do you think you're going, you jerk? You
give them back right now, you whale! Listen, you big
food, I'm not gonna ask again! Stop sinking, I mean it!
My friends and me are on an important adventure! I
can't lose them! Give
them back!
So what do you think? I don't know what to think. Is this
even real? Because I know exactly what I saw and what I
felt. We were swallowed by the whale.
Is this a dream? Yeah, I'd say that's a fair guess.
Then what's with this island and the house?
Illusions.
Looks
like someone's home. Let's hope it's a person. I've
had it! Let's go! Giant squid, guys with harpoons! And
where is Luffy?
I don't know much about whales, but since when do they
have doors and lighted hallways?
A ship. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! We
should fire our cannon there! Now! No. Hold on a sec.
Someone's coming out.