Destiny, fate, dreams. These unstoppable
ideals are held deep in the heart of man.
People tell me my head's in the clouds I
don't care what they say because I'm
I have to follow my dreams, however crazy
they seem. And I won't stop till I get
I'm going to follow my dreams, however
crazy they seem. I'm going to share them
What's wrong, huh? You've had that
brooding look on your face for a while.
No! We're screwed! We've entered the Calm
Belt! The Clam Belt? What's that? Calm
What was that? An earthquake? A good trick
since we're at sea. All of this chit-chat
Look, there's no time to argue. Just shut
up and do as I say. At least it's nice and
Now look! The Grand Line is sandwiched in
the middle between these two green areas
Well, that explains why we haven't gotten
a single gust of wind. How are we going to
Sea monsters! They're gigantic! The Calm
Belt is also home to the Sea Kings! It's
Any idea how we get out of this? Yes.
Everybody, don't move a muscle. We don't
It feels like we're flying! In case you
haven't noticed, we are flying! Oh well,
Isn't this exciting? We're finally going!
We did it! We did it! Cut it out! Sorry.
I'm familiar with the rumors and these
drawings confirm it. As unimaginable as it
Well, the map says otherwise. That's
right, and if Nami thinks something can be
Uh, does this current seem unusually
strong to anyone else? Usopp, what did you
Oh, come on. How could that possibly work?
Look right here. You see? The guiding
The currents would force water up these
canals, collide at the top, and then flow
If we screw up and miss the entrance to
the canal, the Going Mary will be carried
No, that's not my point at all. Anyway,
since we're positioned on this current, we
Whatever we find, it isn't going to be
easy. Sanji, could you get the sale?
Wow! Awesome! It's bigger than I thought!
I can't see the top! It's taller than the
We're getting sucked in! Hold the rudder
steady! We're on it! Nami! Where's that
Nami! Give us a direction! Keep bearing
straight ahead! You can't be serious!
We have to make our way through those
water gates just right! Or we'll crash
Grab a hold! We made it!
Now it's just a straight shot to the
stomach! Wow! Great view! Wow! Look how
We're not in the clouds, we're above them!
It's amazing! We've done it! We've reached
I can see it! This is the greatest sea in
the whole world! The Grand Line! Somewhere
Let's go! Did you guys just hear
something? It was probably just a whiz! At
What's that? Nami! I see a mountain up
ahead! What? That's impossible! But it's
It's a black wall! No, it's not! But what
is it? It's a whale! What are we gonna do?
If this creature looks like a giant wall
to us, we must be a speck! That's right!
This is pointless! The ship's not gonna
turn! Dammit! Don't give up!
Oh, it's good. This is it. Hey, that was
my special scene!
Damn! Let's get out of here before it's
too late! Don't mind telling me what the
Luffy? You think you can break my special
seat? Get away with it! Take it! You
I am not gonna die!
Oh, man. Everyone's been swallowed whole.
Hey, you! Can you hear me? Spit him out! I
You give them back right now, you whale!
Listen, you big food, I'm not gonna ask
So what do you think? I don't know what to
think. Is this even real? Because I know
Looks like someone's home. Let's hope it's
a person.
I've had it. Let's go. Giant squids, guys
with harpoons? And where is Luffy? Yeah,