Destiny, fate, dreams. These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man. As long as there are
people who seek freedom in this life, these things
shall not vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds I don't care what
they say because I'm dreaming of you You are the
treasure I found So bright, so bold, it's so elusive
It's hard to look away Even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe how I feel inside I'm
really, really stuck on you I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem. And I won't stop till I get
there, you will see. You're all I need to have the
strength to believe. Believe in one.
I'm going to follow my dreams, however crazy they
seem. I'm going to share them with you, where love's so
true. You're all I want, together we can move on, live
how we want to. There is no limit to us, we have the power
of love, and we don't want to live ordinary lives. We
have a chance to live in paradise, but even
What's wrong, huh? You've had that brooding look on
your face for a while. Yeah, I guess I hoped I was
dreaming. About what? This may sound crazy, but it
seems to me we're not even moving. You feel that? Now
that you mention it, the sail doesn't appear to be
catching any wind at all.
No! We're screwed! We've entered the Calm Belt! The
Clam Belt? What's that? Calm Belt! A part of the sea
where nothing moves the muscles! So there's muscles
and clams? No!
What was that? An earthquake? A good trick since we're
at sea. All of this chit-chat isn't going to get us out
of here! Fold the sails and start paddling now! We have
to get back on course! You can count on me! Don't panic.
And besides, this is a sailboat. Why do we need to
paddle? True. Look, there's no time to argue. Just
shut up and do as I say. At least it's nice and quiet
here. Fine, if I need to explain it to you, I will. In our
haste to escape from the Marines, we ended up going too
far south, and now we're off course and stuck out here.
So we enter the Grand Line? If we were at the Grand Line,
you think I'd waste my time explaining this? Now look!
The Grand Line is sandwiched in the middle between
these two green areas you see here, you understand?
These areas, just as they're labeled, are what's
called the Calm Belt. That's where we are. Nobody
knows why, but inside the Calm Belt, there's no wind
and no current. It's like a void where everything's
stagnant. Given that sailboats move by catching
winds, this is more than a dangerous region. It can be
fatal, get it? Nope, but it sounds like we're in big
trouble. Well, that explains why we haven't gotten a
single gust of wind. How are we going to get out of this
if our ship can't move? Maybe the wind will start
blowing again. Wind never blows in the Calm Belt. And
that's not all. There's another good reason that
people call this area dangerous. It's infested
with... What was that?
Here they go!
Sea monsters! They're gigantic!
The Calm Belt is also home to the Sea Kings! It's their
main place for breeding! They're the biggest reason
people can't cross the Calm Belt! Any idea how we get
out of this? Yes. Everybody, don't move a muscle. We
don't want to give them any reason to stick around or
eat us. Once they're gone, we'll paddle back. Got it?
You call that a plan?
Shut up! Sorry.
That didn't improve anything! It sounds like it's
gonna! Face yourself, I think this behemoth's gonna
sneeze!
It feels like we're flying! In case you haven't
noticed, we are flying! Oh
well, at least we're back on our original course.
According to the map, we should be spotting the red
line any time now.
Wow, we're almost there! The grand line at last! Isn't
this exciting? We're finally going! We did it! We did
it! Cut it out! Sorry. Zoro! You must be right. Is the
path to the Grand Line really as perilous as it's drawn
here? Stop that!
Take a look. I'm familiar with the rumors and these
drawings confirm it. As unimaginable as it may seem,
the entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain. So what,
did we crash into it? You gotta be kidding. I didn't
believe it, but the map's clear. The mountain appears
to be riddled with small canals, so we might have to go
up and over it. Sounds like fun. What are you talking
about? Even if there are canals or whatever, a ship
can't climb up a mountain. Well, the map says
otherwise. That's right, and if Nami thinks
something can be done, then it can't, got that? Yeah,
but remember, that map was stolen from Buggy the
Clown, so can we trust it? It's still known as the
Rudderstock! A little help over here be nice! Sanji,
would you please give Usopp a hand? I can't think with
all his shouting! Hey, Nami! Okay. Uh, does this
current seem unusually strong to anyone else? Usopp,
what did you just say? I asked if any of you noticed the
insane strength of this current. The current? That
must be... What is it? The canals do go up the mountain.
Oh, come on. How could that possibly work? Look right
here. You see? The guiding light was directing us
toward this spot on the red line. Notice how it's
labeled here, reverse mountain. Hello? Little help
over here, thank you. These green lines represent
canals or artificial waterways. If major currents
from all four oceans flow toward this mountain, what
do you think's going to happen? The currents would
force water up these canals, collide at the top, and
then flow straight down into the Grand Line. Now,
reverse mountain is a winter mountain, so it's cold,
right? That means any surface currents that don't
flow up the canal will be forced down as they cool.
Anything riding those currents would be pulled down
as well. If we screw up and miss the entrance to the
canal, the Going Mary will be carried straight into
the Red Line's rock face and likely be destroyed. Ship
and crew would be sucked to the bottom of the sea.
Understand? Yeah, basically it's a mystery
mountain. No, that's not my point at all. Anyway,
since we're positioned on this current, we shouldn't
run into any problems getting to the summit of Reverse
Mountain. Only thing that would hurt us now is if
something went wrong with the rudder. Nami, you're a
genius! Call me a skeptic, but ships do not climb
mountains. Well, I've heard a few stories. Stories
about the Mystery Mountain? No. What I have heard is
that more than half the people who try to make it to the
Grand Line die before they even get there. Whatever we
find, it isn't going to be easy. Sanji, could you get
the sale? Anything for you, Nami! Luffy, help me!
Got it!
Hey! I can see the Mystery Mountain!
That's insanely huge! Wow! Awesome! It's bigger than
I thought! I can't see the top! It's taller than the
clouds!
We're getting sucked in! Hold the rudder steady!
We're on it! Nami!
Where's that entrance you were talking about? If we
keep this heading, we're gonna crash into the rock!
There's a crack in that cliff. That must be it. Nami!
Give us a direction! Keep bearing straight ahead! You
can't be serious! Trust me! Have we made it? Is that the
canal entrance? More than likely. I've gotta be
dreaming. It's impossible. The ocean really is
flowing up the mountain.
We have to make our way through those water gates just
right! Or we'll crash into the red line if he's smashed
to pieces!
We're drifting off course! Gotta go more to the right!
Right! The right? Who hit starboard?
Come on now! Put your back into it!
That's
water! Oh no!
Grab
a hold!
We made it!
Now it's just a straight shot to the stomach! Wow!
Great view!
Wow! Look how high we are! We're in the clouds!
We're not in the clouds, we're above them!
It's amazing! We've done it! We've reached the
summit!
I
can see
it! This is the greatest sea in the whole world! The
Grand Line! Somewhere out there the One Piece is
waiting and we're gonna find it! Let's
go! Did you guys just hear something? It was probably
just a whiz! At this speed, everything sounds
distorted!
What's that? Nami! I see a mountain up ahead! What?
That's impossible! But it's right there! I can see it!
Who cares? Go! After we pass the twin caves up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
It's a black wall! No, it's not! But what is it?
It's a whale! What are we gonna do? Should we fight?
Idiots, how are we supposed to fight a hundred ton
whale? Do something! Our path is blocked! How do we
escape? Calm down. If this creature looks like a giant
wall to us, we must be a speck! That's right! It's
highly possible that this thing isn't even aware that
we're here! We'll run right into it unless we change
course! Look! We can get by on the left! Port! Port to
port! The rudder's broken! Do something! Anything!
Wait! I know! This'll work! It has to! Hey! Luffy! What
are you doing?
This is pointless! The ship's not gonna turn! Dammit!
Don't give up!
Oh, it's good. This is
it. Hey, that was my special scene!
Damn! Let's get out of here before it's too late! Don't
mind telling me what the heck is going on! It's so big
that the cannonball didn't even make it flinch. That
or his reaction time's really slow. Who cares? At
least we're alive!
My ears! Just battle! We have to get away from here!
Luffy? You think you can break my special seat? Get
away with it! Take it! You moron!
I'm not through with you! There's a lot more with it!
Shut up before you kill us!
I
am
not gonna
die!
Oh, man. Everyone's been swallowed whole. Hey, you!
Can you hear me? Spit him out! I want my friends! Damn
you! Where do you think you're going, you jerk? You
give them back right now, you whale! Listen, you big
food, I'm not gonna ask again! Stop sinking, I mean it!
My friends and me are on an important adventure! I
can't lose them! Give them back!
So what do you think? I don't know what to think. Is this
even real? Because I know exactly what I saw and what I
felt. We were swallowed by the whale.
Is this a dream? Yeah, I'd say that's a fair guess.
Then what's with this island and the house?
Illusions.
Looks
like someone's home. Let's hope it's a person. I've
had it. Let's go. Giant squids, guys with harpoons?
And where is Luffy?
Yeah, where is he? I don't know much about whales, but
since when do they have doors and lighted hallways?
A ship. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! We
should fire our cannon there! No! No. Hold on a sec.
Someone's coming out.