I can't believe it. I can't
believe it.
How was it, Zoro? It's hard to
face from just before. No, I
don't think so. What? It's
from just before. I feel like
this ship doesn't move.
What? I mean, Hoga doesn't
have a wind.
It's over! I got into the carm
belt! What's that? Carm
belt! It's the name of the
carm belt! What's the name of
the carm belt? What's the
name of the carm belt? What's
the name of the carm belt?
What's the name of the carm
belt? What's the name of the
carm belt? What's the name of
the carm belt? What's the
name of the carm belt? What's
the name of the carm belt?
What are you doing? It's a
ship. It's a ship. That's
right. Don't you tell me what
you're saying. It's a
difficult thing. It's not a
ship. Well, I'll explain it.
Okay? I'm going to go away
from this ship, so I'm going
to go to the front of the ship.
So, Grand Line in? Wow!
That's how easy it is! That's
good! The Grand Line that
we're looking for are more
than 2 different areas. Do
you understand? This 2
different areas are called
the Carmel Belt. I don't know
why, but if it doesn't, it
doesn't have a river. It's a
complete state of the state
of the sea! It's a dangerous
place for the wind! It's a
dangerous place for the
wind! Did you understand it?
Yes, it's a difficult thing.
It's the only way that the
wind blows up. You can't do
it. You can't do it. You can't
do it. You can't do it. That's
why! If you enter the sea of
the sea of the sea of the sea of
the sea!
Wow!
Wow! Wow!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! How
are you going to do this
situation? Let's go,
everyone. I'll go back to the
ship, so I'll go back
to the ship.
I'm going to go back to the
ship. I'm going to go back to
the ship. I'm going to go back
to the ship. I'm going to go
back to the ship. I'm going to
go back to the ship. I'm going
back to the ship.
Really, I'm going to
fly! It's like you came back
to the original road. It's
time to see a red line.
It's the Grand Line!
It's the same thing!
It's the same thing! It's the
same thing! It's the same
thing! It's the
same thing!
I've heard of it, but I've
heard of it, but I've heard of
it as well. If it's like that,
the Grand Line is a mountain.
The mountain? The mountain?
What did you say? What did you
say? I thought I was thinking
about it, but there's a
mountain on the mountain.
It's a mountain on the
mountain. It's a mountain on
the mountain. Oh, that's
interesting. What are you
saying? The mountain on the
mountain is climbing on the
mountain. That's it, it's
written in there. So, that's
what you're saying! That's
what you're buying from
Buggies, right? That's what
you're saying. What's that?
Don't worry! Don't worry,
don't worry, don't worry,
don't worry It's... It's...
It's...
It's... It's... It's...
It's... It's...
It's... Red Line in the river
mountain. What are you
doing? There is a sea sea sea
sea sea sea sea sea sea sea sea
sea sea The reverse mountain
is a spring island, so the red
line of the river is on the
coast from the coast of the
coast of the coast. If you
don't know about the boat,
the Boeing Marine号 is on the
edge of the coast of the
coast, and the ship is
destroyed. It's like the sea
of the moxu, right? Yes, I
see. It's a strange
mountain, isn't it? Well, I
don't know. But anyway,
we're going to get into the
sea, so if we're going to get
to the river mountain
mountain, we'll be able to go
mountain. Oh, wow! I didn't
hear that. I've heard of a
mountain in the sea. I have a
little bit. What's that? No.
Grand Line is going to go in
the front of us, but we don't
know if we can't. We don't
know if we can't. Come on,
please! Yes,
Nani! Come on, Nani! Come on,
Nani! Come on, Nani! Wow!
That's the best
line! There's no one in the
sky!
Oh, that崖
of
hibber!
How are you? Go ahead! Go
ahead! I'll do it! I'll do it!
I'll do it! I'll do it! I'll do
it! I'll do it!
it! I'll do it! I'll do it!
I'll do it! I'll do it! I'll do
it!
It's not going to
go!
Take
it!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Wow!
It's
in
the sky! Wow! Look! It's on
top! Look! It's on top! It's
on top!
Look! This is the most
beautiful sea of the world!
The Grand Line! There's one
piece in this place!
Do you hear anything? It's
not a wind sound.
There are many places there.
What? There's a mountain!
There's a mountain! There's
no mountain! There's no
mountain! There's no
mountain!
What's that? What's that?
What's
that? What's that? What's
that? What's that? Sokka, I
don't have to know what
you're doing! You're stuck
with me! Hey! I'm going to go
left! I'm going to go! I'm
going to go! I'm going to go!
I'm going to go! I'm going to
go! I'm going to go! I'm going
to go! I'm going to go! I'm
going to go!
I
can't
do it! I can't do it!
I can't do it!
I can't do it! Okay, did you
stop?
I...
I... I...
I... I... I... I...
I...
Let's go! Let's go! What the
hell are you doing? I'm not
going to kill you! I'm not
going to kill you! I'm
not going to kill you! I'm not
going to kill you! I'm not
going
to kill you! Luffy? What are
you going to do with me?
What are you going to do with
me?
I... I... I... I... I... I...
I'll be back! I'll be back!
What
do you think? What do you
think? What do you think?
What do you think? What do you
What do you think?
So, what is that island and
house? It's a幻,
right? So, what is this?
There's a lot of people,
right? It's a lot of people,
but... I don't want to go
back.
I'm going back to Ruffy. How
is it going? So, Ruffy...
What is this? Why do
you have a door on a horse and a
door on a horse? What's that?
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Just wait. Someone
came out.